Raghu !
Where is he ?
Where are you wood stealer ? - Yes brother .
Until I don 't abuse you , you don 't listen .
I thought that of the witch palace , gobbled you up .
Did you finish the work ?
It will be over tomorrow , brother .
He is going to arrive today from America .
A bit of colour , a bit of polish that 's all .
But no , you have been working on it for past one month ...
... like there is no end to it .
What can I do , no one is ready to work in this haunted palace .
I have gathered 4-5 artists .
But everyone runs away after ...
... the sunset out of fear . Tell me what to do ?
Okay , okay .
When the cot is polished , keep it there .
Does it look like a cot to you , it is a bed , a royal bed .
When 5-6 strong men will use their complete strength ...
... only then will it budge .
Give me some money , I will call ...
... some people and take care of it right now .
Did you water the garden yesterday or not ?
No , it was raining yesterday .
Then you could have held a umbrella and watered it .
One is a wood thief and the other , useless .
And don 't make excuses , that if you take more days ...
... then you will earn more .
It is a royal family , we will plunder it .
Thieves .
Did you sell the carpet here ?
The rein is gone , so are the kings .
Now even the honour is disintegrating .
Seems like I will have to get the curtains that I gave for stitching .
They are not what they seem .
How much do I have to pay you Raghu ?
How much ?
Raghu .
Raghu !
He goes after that one and ...
Mr. Nath ! Mr. Nath !
Have you seen my Murari uncle ?
No .
When he comes , ask him to come home .
The bucket has fallen in the well , it has to be taken out .
Okay , I will tell him .
Don 't forget it . - I won 't .
Sir , sir . You have arrived at the right moment .
It was a good game going on ...
... when the English men started mumbling again .
Please tell us what the score is ?
197 runs and 3 wickets .
We should ban this English language ...
... nothing can be understood .
Do you know , unknowingly how much English you speak .
You don 't even know the Hindi meaning of some English words .
Tell me , what do you call cricket in Hindi ?
Cricket is called ...
So son-in-law , what 's going on ?
The same old argument between Hindi and English .
Hind , Hindi is the best .
How do you write cat in English . - How ?
C A T. How do you pronounce it ? Cat . What does it mean ?
Cat .
Now in Hindi , they read , write and mean it in the same way .
Good , good .
But Sanskrit is the mother of all languages .
Now tell me this ... Mood talam kunchika kim .
What will it mean in Hindi ?
Think , I will go to the college .
The question is wrong itself .
Mood talam . That means a foolish lock .
A lock cannot be either foolish or smart .
A lock is a lock .
A key is a key .
Like the key to the manor that I have .
Now ...
The manor keys .
" Hail Rama ! Hail Rama !
" Rama Rama Hail Hail ! "
" Hail Krishna ! Hail Krishna ! "
" Krishna Krishna Hail Hail ! "
Murari , why are you dancing off-beat ?
What happened ?
Nandini has been searching for you , do you know . - Why ?
The bucket has to be taken out of the well . Go ! Hurry up !
Then I will have to go .
Or else sister-in-laws rituals will be left incomplete .
Okay , bye .
" Hail Rama ! Hail Rama ! " Rama Rama Hail Hail ! "
Mr. Batuk , what are you doing sitting here ?
Where are you going ? - Mr. Batuk , I was coming to you .
What happened , did you retrieve it ?
I was thinking should I go now and retrieve it , or not .
How did you know ?
Me . How wouldn 't I know !
Your daughter told me .
My daughter . - Yes .
How did she know ?
Sister-in-law must have told her .
She knows it too , now she will scold me .
It is a personal thing , why are you worried .
I will take it out , come on .
Brother Murari , you are very brave . - You just come with me .
I was thinking of retrieving it tomorrow .
But I was very restless .
It is the humid season , that 's why .
Pour 10 buckets of cold water saying ' Hail Gange ' .
You will feel very nice , our work will be done .
Tell me one thing , won 't you be scared in the darkness .
What is there to be scared of , I just have to jump in the well .
In the well , why in the well ?
The bucket is in the well .
Bucket ? - Yes .
The keys are in the manor .
Then what do I have to take out , key , bucket or well .
You fool , my keys are in the manor I have to get that back !
Keys . - Yes
In the manor . - Yes .
Right now . - Yes .
In this darkness .
No , I am not coming .
You were acting very brave , now I will not let you go .
Come on , come on . - No ! No !
Why are you walking around in circles ?
I have asked for a protection shield from the junior priest .
I have been standing here since morning .
Now I cannot even sit .
My stomach is getting restless .
The 1000 name recitation is going on , it will take time .
I hope I am not too late . It will take time .
Batuk . - Priest , priest .
What you saw was true .
That witch is really roaming around in the manor .
Your lifeline was long , that 's why you returned alive .
But I have enslaved many dangerous ghosts .
Respected Yogi , my teacher has blessed me with his grace .
Tie this talisman on the tree in the south side of the manor .
That witch will turn to ashes .
Om !
Do you want to say anything for the last time ?
Last time , why are you hanging me by the noose ?
From taking talisman in your hand and until tying it to the tree ...
... you cannot say anything .
Then what about the work ... - Quiet !
Shut your mouth ! Om !
Om !
Mr. Batuk , where did you disappear to last night ?
I was tired of searching for you , but you were no where to be seen .
Okay , if I wouldn 't have been there you would have been more scared .
You are still not saying anything .
No , no now will know about your scare .
I am keeping my lips sealed .
What ?
Which is this dance that you are doing ?
What happened ?
You want to sit at the back .
Seems like you have lost your mind ...
... after seeing the witch last night , right
What ?
What has happened ?
What are you writing ?
Stomach upset , let 's go home .
Oh ! So you want to go now .
I thought you must have soiled your clothes last night .
Am going , I will take you .
Sister-in-law ! Janki sister-in-law .
What is it ? - Why are you shouting ?
Forget about me , tell me did Batuk tell you anything last night ?
No , he came home late scared and went back early in the morning .
That means he didn 't say anything .
He didn 't open his mouth .
My suspicion was right .
After last nights incident in the manor , he has lost his voice ...
... like Madan 's daughter , Girja .
Oh God , what happened in the manor ?
What I said ?
Many a times I have told him not to go to the manor in the night .
But he doesn 't listen to me at all .
Where is he right now , in the hospital ?
Didn 't you see , he just went running in .
Cheeks blown up . Red eyes , and he was walking as if ...
... someone has cast him on a stick .
Take a look at him when he comes .
Listen , what happened ?
How many times have I asked you not to go to the manor in the night !
But you don 't listen to me at all !
Tell me ! What happened ? Say something .
Brother Murari , what is he saying now ?
Did you see sister-in-law , since morning he has been ...
... dancing like this out of tune .
1 or 2 won 't do any good .
We will have to get him 10-12 electric shocks .
He is insane since childhood .
Brother Murari , look where is he going ?
I will see where will he go ?
I will got to brother Badri and take the veneration talisman .
Give me . - Take it , take it , take it .
Take it , take it , take it . - I will break your teeth .
Ask your future husband , instead of printing poems , print notes ...
... it will be useful in your marriage .
Take it ... Will you give it or not ?
What 's going on , is this a house or a playground ?
Nothing , nothing . - Runaway from here .
Brother , I want to talk to you . - What is it Janki ?
So it has happened !
I had said , don 't be greedy !
Taking the manors responsibility , will not benefit you , I had told you .
I don 't know how your husband must have persuaded Siddharth ...
... and swindled his money for the repairs of the manor .
And he must have kept half of the money .
But under no condition will I let him live in that manor .
He is coming from America .
After Kedar , he is the heir to the royal throne .
We will have to protect him .
And we have to get her and Siddharth married too .
She has been hoping for that for such a long time .
After Siddharth marries her , we will sell the haunted manor .
Save my husband , brother .
I will give a thread chanting some recitations .
Tell Batuk Shankar to wear it for 3 days .
But will he wear it if I give it ?
You are looking so beautiful .
Your cheeks are rosy red .
In the happiness of Siddharth 's arrival , isn 't it ?
Here , and tie it firmly around Batuk 's stomach .
And until this is not done keep your mouth shut .
Strange , you were supposed to come ...
... yesterday , but arrived today itself .
Actually we had arrived last night .
We went straight to the palace , it was open ...
... the lock was hanging and the key was there too .
We went inside but there was no one .
It was quite late in the night , so we stopped in the hotel .
I thought why I should trouble you .
As soon as it was morning , I came here .
Last night you had entered the palace .
We did .
Avni , why are you standing there come in .
This is my surprise for you .
It has been 10 days to our marriage .
Greetings .
Why are you all so shocked , don 't you want to welcome daughter-in-law ?
Yes .
Uncle , I had said after father he played the role of father .
Bless you .
Radha , you have grown up . And beautiful too .
There wasn 't a single day when we didn 't argue .
If we fought today , we would become friends the next day .
I 've heard a lot about you .
Janki aunt , how are you ?
How is uncle ?
Today is her oath of silence . She has the sacred thread .
Janki , go home . Go .
Brother Kedar was a great astrologer .
According to him , your and Radha 's horoscope ...
... was like made for each other .
All of us wanted you to marry Radha .
I know , mother had told me .
For how many days have you come here ?
For some months .
My company has got a contract ...
... of building a dam here .
So I had to come .
So Avni was very excited .
She will see around here , and I will toil day and night .
Okay , you can live in Chandu 's room .
Uncle , we want to live in the manor .
Avni likes manors and palace 's very much .
That 's why we got the manor repaired .
Look Siddharth , according to the division ...
... even though you are the owner of the manor ...
... but we live here .
That manor is infested by ghost and ghouls .
Uncle , you believe in your faith ...
... and I believe only in the truth .
When I will experience it , I will believe it .
Protect me Lord Shiva .
Wow , now you can use your tongue .
Now I will use my hand too , deserter !
You ran away scared , and were telling everyone that I was scared .
You 're going to shock me .
Mother !
Mother ! - But you ...
No ... no ... have mercy mother !
Murari uncle , she is Siddharth 's wife .
Sister-in-law Avni .
Greetings . - Greetings .
Go away ! Go away you witch , go away !
Have you developed a new habit of scaring people ?
Why are you closing the door ?
I will come home .
Say something . What is it ?
Kiss , I will not give it here .
I won 't give it here no matter what you do ?
Stop ! Stop !
Finished .
Nandini saw everything .
Tell her that you were tying a talisman ...
... or else who knows what she might think . Go !
Only a king can stay in this palace .
After brother Kedar , you are the real heir to this throne .
But you have still not been coroneted .
Uncle , the kings are gone and so are the British .
Now there is democracy in India .
If the reign is over , is the family finished too .
I left all that behind in America .
Do you believe in rituals ...
... or did you leave that behind in America too ?
I do , I believe in them uncle .
You are my king , uncle .
I will do what you ask me to .
Unbelievable !
You are really a king , my king .
Come on Siddharth , dance with me .
Siddharth .
" The king felt in love with the queen . "
A gift for the king , to make me the queen .
What good is this for such a big king ?
" Kiss me on my lips . "
" What are you , tell me now . "
" Surrender yourself in my arms ...
... in my arms , in my arms . "
" The intoxicating fragrance in your emotions , in your fragrant breath . "
" I have a desire to sleep in your silky arms , your scattered breath . "
" Hide the face with another one . "
" Let me hear your heartbeat . "
" See yourself , in my eyes ...
... in my eyes , in my eyes . "
" Kiss me on my lips . "
" What are you , tell me now . "
You have turned our room into a library .
I am a book worm .
I read two books a day .
But I need a good room to keep these books .
I will show you , but what will I get in return ?
Book . What do you like ?
Stories , history or poetry ?
Poetry .
Remember , I am giving you the reward before the work is done .
Here .
My most favourite poetry 's .
This , sister-in-law are you teasing me ?
No , these are really very nice poems .
As if you don 't know anything . - No , what ?
Nandini , listen .
You are shying so much , tell me .
My marriage has been fixed .
With Sharad Prahlad .
He is my favourite poet .
He is a lecturer in our college .
Then he surely writes a lot of poetry on you , isn 't it ?
Come I will show you ? - What ?
There .
He lives there .
The one that 's strolling there ?
The library room . - Yes , come on .
Why is there a chain here ?
We are not allowed to go up there .
But why ?
They say there are ghosts there . - Ghosts .
We don 't even come in this palace .
Sister-in-law .
No sister-in-law . - Come on .
I will not come . Come on .
Sister-in-law , don 't go .
Let us see , who is living in our house without our permission
Come on .
What is this ?
The Bhairav shield .
So that the ghost doesn 't come out .
Come on , sister-in-law . - Really ?
Don 't laugh sister-in-law , this place is really dangerous .
In the childhood , we were playing hide and seek ...
... and Girja came here to hide .
Then we heard her scream .
When we came up and searched for her , she was nowhere to be found .
But when Badri uncle and father searched for her in the evening ...
... she was found unconscious right here .
Since then she has stopped talking .
Everyone says that she has been taken over by ghosts .
Come sister-in-law , we will go from here .
Where is the key to this lock ?
With my father , but don 't even think about asking for it .
You are excused everything , and I will be thrashed .
Think about it , I have another good book of your Sharad .
Do you want it ? - Really .
Nandini !
Nand ...
Come here ! You come here !
You know it , don 't you ?
Daughter-in-law is new here but you know ...
... that it is not allowed to go to the third floor .
Have you lost your senses ?
Daughter-in-law . - Yes .
Remember one thing .
65 years ago , all the rooms of that floor were closed ...
... with magic and mantra .
Two souls reside there .
Educated people will make fun of it .
But nowadays , foreign scientists have started believing in it .
It has ruined many of our lives .
And this is true . What is the use in challenging the souls of the dead ?
All these veneration and offerings is for those two souls .
But who were those two people ?
It is a very old story .
Years ago , king Vibhuti Narayan .
Meaning , your Siddharth 's ancestors ...
... he used to rule here .
He was a great admirer of art .
He had a very big court .
Well known singers , dancers , poets , painters ...
... were in his court .
Many foreign artists would come and leave with riches .
Then came Bengal 's great dancer , Manjulika .
They say she was very gorgeous looking .
The old king fell for her .
Vibhuti Narayan was floored .
The king would neither care for the kingdom or his reign .
But Manjulika loved someone else . - The royal singer .
Her name was Shashidhar .
The house that is behind our palace , he used to live there .
Their love started developing slyly .
But the aroma of clarified butter and love , can never be hidden .
The king found out about it .
The night both of them were about to flee ...
... the king called Manjulika to dance in his court .
It was the eight day of the Goddess Durga veneration .
Manjulika was dancing .
Suddenly , the king drew his sword ...
... and beheaded Shashidhar in front of everyone ...
... and locked up Manjulika .
The king started the preparations for the marriage .
The dias was setup , the arrangements were made .
As the slaves went up to bring the bride ...
... they found her hanging from the ceiling .
And along was a letter .
In that she had sworn , that she will ...
... never let a king live in this palace .
After that it seemed like someone has cast an evil eye ...
... on the kings kingdom .
There was destruction in the kingdom .
One day the king was found dead too .
Then a very big sorcerer was called .
Mantras were recited for 7 days continuously .
And by putting the Bhairav shield both the souls ...
... were locked on the third floor .
Since then no one goes there .
Do you know who lives in Shashidhar 's house now ?
Who ? - Sharad , Nandini 's future husband .
Is this entire story or a reality .
I don 't know , there are such secrets in every king 's kingdom .
It is a nice story . - Very interesting .
The villagers must have made it for their entertainment .
You know , your mother had said ...
... that there is a very big treasure in this palace .
There are gold and diamond jewels too .
I looked all around the palace , but I couldn 't find it .
Maybe it is hidden in that room .
And I feel , they must have made this story to hide that treasure .
Can I open that room ?
It is your house , do whatever you like .
Avni !
That was not the right thing to do Avni .
Father had said no , still you opened the door .
I opened it and also saw it .
I couldn 't see any ghost there .
You must have not seen it , because the effect has started .
The blacksmith who made the keys , he has died .
Do you know what you have done ? You !
You cannot even take care of a key ...
... how will you carry out the responsibility of the palace !
Your daughter stole your key and made a duplicate one ...
... and Siddharth 's wife opened the lock of the door .
Couldn 't you even think once ?
Nandu ! Nandu ! Nandu ! Always Nandu !
What are you doing , she is just a child .
Just because they can talk in English ...
... they think that they can interfere in any matter .
Years ago she had gone to the 3rd floor , she is still shocked .
Who knows what will happen now ?
Sister , is everything fine ? Any problem ?
It has come , or is about to come we don 't know .
What are you looking at me for standing here ...
... go and call the high priest ! Only he can save us from this problem !
You said yes , now face the consequences !
I told you , I don 't believe in these things .
Then go to the crematorium and see .
The blacksmith is lying on the pyre .
I have found out , that drunkard blacksmith ...
... died because of liver failure and not because of a ghost .
Nandini is withering with fever .
You all must have scared her .
What happened , did you find out when the high priest is going to come .
He has gone to London .
Oh God ! To some college called Trimurty .
Not Trimurty uncle , Trinity . Trinity University . - Yes .
He has gone to read some paper there ...
... and no one knows when he will return .
Lord Shiva .
But why has he gone to London to read a paper ?
You get all the papers at the village square .
It means he has gone to teach there .
But , who is this gentleman ?
He is a very big sorcerer .
Priest Yagyaprakash Bharti .
Years ago , his grandfather priest Vedsagar ...
... had put the Bhairav shield and closed the door .
Priest Yagyaprakash must be 15-16 years old ...
... but he was intelligent .
He was his grandfather 's aide .
Priest Yagyaprakash is the only one ...
... that can complete this ritual .
Until priest Yagyaprakash doesn 't put the Bhairav shield ...
... on the door and closes it .
It is very dangerous to live here .
It is a strange maze of delusion , blind faith and mental games .
Brother Badri , my heart is very restless .
Nandini is about to get married .
And something inauspicious should not happen before that .
Don 't worry Batuk Shankar , it 's my responsibility .
If Siddharth wants to live here , then all of us will live here .
Uncle ... - That 's my duty .
You both are alone , it is a new city for you .
If something happens , you need the family close .
Whatever happens , we will bear it together .
Make arrangements for everyone to come here . - Yes brother .
Your saris are very beautiful .
You can keep whichever you want , they are all yours .
Maid , call the tailor .
We will have the blouse stitched . - Yes .
Then you can wear them whenever you want .
Poison .
It is for the rats .
They must have infested the empty house .
Leave it , it 's dangerous .
Maid . - Yes .
Keep this poison in the kitchen carefully . - Yes . Thank you .
Who is it ?
Who is there ? - I am Manjulika !
You kept me locked up for so many years !
How dare you ?
Run ! Run !
Who is it ?
Who ?
Siddharth ! Siddharth ! Siddharth get up !
Siddharth ! - What happened ?
Siddharth !
You know that santi ? - Who santi ?
That maid , she is crying of fear . - What happened ?
She says that she has seen the ghost . - What nonsense ?
Come on quickly .
What happened ?
She saw something and was scared .
What did you see ?
I was sleeping right here .
Suddenly I woke up .
A sound anklets was coming from somewhere .
When I looked , it was her
Scattered hair .
She was peeking from the hole .
You were saying that there was darkness outside .
What can you see clearly in the darkness ?
What were you thinking while sleeping ?
It is all your illusion .
What happened ? - What happened ?
Who broke it !
How is all this happening ?
Who is doing all this ?
It is black magic .
Someone has cast a spell .
Stop your nonsense !
All these things cannot happen without someone doing it .
Talking all lies .
Ghosts and ghouls , magic spells , go inside all of you !
Close the door and go to sleep !
Walk in a group . Walk in a group .
I am not ashamed to say that I am scared .
Chandu , who has appointed these servants .
Mother has , but what happened ?
What happened , first ask aunt to fire that maid !
I don 't want anyone who spreads rumours about the palace .
What is all this commotion , what has happened ?
Some strange things are happening .
Someone is playing a dirty trick .
But what has happened ?
Nothing , I was ... - The maid saw the palace 's ghost there .
There .
What 's happening ?
Are you fine ?
Siddharth ! Siddharth !
Who must have broken all this ?
I had shot so many things in this !
Our arrival , your coronation .
Say something Siddharth .
I opened that door , that 's why all this is happening isn 't it ?
Why will this ghost named Manjulika break our video camera ?
Surely there is something . - I am also sure of it .
Uncle I want to talk to you .
Do you still want to say something ?
All that happened in front of you in the palace ...
... isn 't that enough as evidence for you .
The worst is about to come .
I request to you , be sensible and let 's go from here .
You are saying it without knowing what happened and who did it , uncle !
I know what the reality is , and that 's what I have come to tell you !
When it 's time to run you are searching for maps .
Uncle , you don 't understand .
What happened ? What happened ?
Avni , what happened ? Open your eyes , Avni .
Chandu , quickly call the doctor .
Call the doctor .
Quickly make a call . - Pick her up quickly .
Take her to the hospital .
- Call the doctor otherwise it will be too late .
Pick her up .
Take her to the room .
Avni ! Avni ! Avni ! Avni ! Avni !
Avni !
Are you fine ?
What happened ? How did this happen ?
I don 't know .
Suddenly my veil started burning .
Ask Radha , she saw it .
When I saw , the veil was burning .
Lord Shiva .
She is saved .
Please you people ... Go , bring a sari .
Uncle , I want to talk to you .
What is it ?
Uncle , if you don 't mind can I ask you something ?
Tell me clearly what you want to .
Uncle , I wanted to ask ... how is Radha ?
Does she have any mental ailment or any mental tension ?
Adopted children can have mental ailments .
Had something happened before ?
It is not something to hide , nor to feel shy .
Mental ailments can be treated .
We will call a good doctor .
Keep quiet , are you in your senses . What are you saying ?
These are the deeds of your wife with modern thoughts and yours .
And you are blaming my daughter .
If we say anything to you , you don 't want to believe it .
Will you believe it ?
Last night , we have touched death and returned back alive .
Me , Murari and Natwar had gone there .
Thinking that let the priest come at his own time ...
... before that we will perform the veneration ...
... and keep the auspicious pot .
Do you know , we heard Manjulika 's voice .
We even heard the sound of her anklets .
Now say that the three of us are mad ...
... and put us in a mental asylum .
So you have seen the ghost too .
Fools are never called intelligent .
Because he has never seen the sunlight .
Don 't feel bad about my anger .
I am talking about everyone 's betterment .
And your betterment is in that you pack your bags ...
... and come to my manor . Right now .
And please don 't think this is my misbehavior .
I am very strong of my principles .
Myself and Avni are not going anywhere .
I just want to do something for Radha , let me do it .
What happened ?
He is not ready to leave the palace !
What ?
He is not ready to believe , because of daughter-in-law ...
... ghosts have been let free in this palace .
He is telling me , that Radha has some mental illness .
O God . - You keep quiet .
Just because he said it doesn 't mean anything .
What could have happened to Radha ?
Go and ask him ! Your son-in-law .
It is a mental sickness , what else .
What happened now brother ?
What happened ?
This , this is the blouse that you have made ? ! - Yes . Why ?
Quit working as a tailor , your method is wrong . - What happened ?
Go take them back and stitch them properly and bring them back .
I would have never cut it like this .
First I will cut one hand , then the other .
And finally I will cut the throat , understood or not ?
Oh God !
What happened uncle , did you have any work ?
Brother Badri . - What ?
What ?
What Siddharth said was right . - What ?
The palace 's ghost has entered her , it won 't leave her easily .
I saw her , knife in the hand , scattered hair ...
... and she pounced on to me with the knife .
Don 't talk nonsense .
I am telling the truth .
You don 't believe it , come on I will show ...
What happened ? - Nothing , you are absolutely fine .
Nothing has happened to you , nothing .
Sit , sit .
Yes , keep swinging .
Day and night , just keep swinging .
You don 't want to swing . - It 's okay you can stop .
Am I mad that I will keep swinging all day ?
Why are you crying , aunt ?
Even mother has been crying since morning .
Uncle ! - Nothing , nothing .
Why are you all staring at me ?
You tell me , why is everyone staring at me ?
Tell me .
Someone tell me what 's happening ?
Tell me !
Hello , hello , hello may I speak with Aditya Srivastav please ?
Yes , its urgent .
This is his friend from India , Siddharth .
Greetings madam , Mrs. Sharma this is Siddharth here .
There was a very important thing , I wanted to talk about a patient .
Yes , his ...
I tried his mobile , it is switched off .
He didn 't answer my e-mail , that 's why I called the hospital .
Please give him the message that the patients condition ...
... is getting worse day by day . Ask him to call me . It 's urgent .
Okay , thank you ma 'am .
Radha is not uncle Badri 's daughter ?
No , she has been adopted .
Radha 's father was the royal astrologer ...
... and brother Badri 's very good friend .
After his death , she was completely helpless .
Her mother had passed away in her childhood .
Then brother Badri adopted her and brought her up as his daughter .
You know , in childhood Siddharth and Radha were very good friends .
Everyone wanted Radha and Siddharth to get married .
Radha dreamt about that too .
But Siddharth married you and Radha was heart broken .
The ghost has entered Radha .
That means , that old king must be wandering somewhere around .
Troublesome ghost , don 't trouble me , don 't trouble me .
Or else I will thrust this in , I am telling the truth ...
... I will thrust it in .
Don 't trouble me .
I am not from this family , I got married that 's why I am with them ...
... I am not from this family .
Why are you troubling me ?
No ! No ! No ! No !
Don 't come near me .
Don 't come ...
No ! No !
No ! No ! No !
Don 't come near me . No . No .
You were saying about him , isn 't it ?
He is in a very dangerous stage .
And why have you left him open ?
Tie him to a pole .
Who is this beggar ? - Beggar .
Leave him , he is my uncle .
He could be , but he is ill .
No , he is not ill .
He started piercing me with the umbrella calling me old king .
That 's why I caught him .
Uncle he is my friend Aditya , he has come from America .
He is a psychiatrist .
Ask him to treat himself first .
I am perfectly fine . Good that you ...
... arrived on time , or else he would have strangled me .
I am sorry .
Sorry .
This is the invention of the English .
First commit a mistake and then say sorry to commit another mistake .
When did you arrive ?
And how did you manage to reach here ?
I called you so many times , faxed you , e-mailed you ...
... but you didn 't reply to anything . Where were you absconding ?
And what is the new garb that you have worn .
Nothing , I was in the Kumbh fair .
For the past 15-20 days I have been taking a dip ...
... and washing of my sins .
You cannot do that wearing jeans and T-shirt . That 's why .
My secretary informed me that you had called ...
... that 's why I came here running . And ...
I have to pay the auto-rickshaw too .
Ramnath , how much do I have to pay ? - 13,000 .
Repeat it louder . - 13,000 !
13,000 . - Yes , I have come from Allahabad in the auto-rickshaw .
Even I enjoyed driving it .
I told the driver to sit behind and I 'd drive .
I put the key in and started .
Patient .
Patient , patient .
Uncle , this is my friend Aditya .
He is psychic ... he is a psychiatrist , uncle ...
" Hail Rama ! Hail Rama ! "
Greetings uncle .
My daughter is not insane . - Yes uncle .
Please don 't make her insane . - Yes uncle .
" Hail Krishna ! Hail Rama ! "
And then when I drove the rickshaw . And while driving it I ...
Brother !
What happened ?
I saw her , she ran away seeing me .
There is something wrong .
I can see in her eyes something is wrong .
Whom did you see ? - That middle-aged one .
She will be fine , no matter .
You must have seen aunt Janki and not Radha .
Everyone seems to be insane .
Have you opened a mental asylum here ?
It is not their fault , it is because of your getup .
You look more like a impostor than a doctor .
You know I get bored treating patients in the hospital .
Whenever I get the chance I freak out , wear such strange clothes .
Come on , freshen up quickly .
Introduce me to sister-in-law .
Yes , Avni . - Avni .
Have you seen sister-in-law Avni ? - No .
Nandini listen . - Yes .
I might have seen her go up with a book .
Yes , she has gone up . - Okay .
Sister-in-law .
Sister-in-law Avni .
Open this door .
It won 't open like that , we will have to break it . Come .
123 .
Has the doctor arrived ? - Yes , he is inside .
Good .
Oh brother ...
Who is he ?
There has been blood loss .
That 's why there will be weakness for some days .
Otherwise , there is nothing to worry about .
Everything will be fine .
How did you get seriously wounded , dear ?
I had gone up to look for sister-in-law Avni .
I felt that someone is following me .
Who ? - I couldn 't see anyone .
I reached the court running .
There suddenly , the swing hit my head .
Like somebody had pushed it .
After that , I don 't remember anything .
But who told you that I am upstairs ?
I was not there .
Sister Radha .
Radha ?
Why , I had gone to take a bath .
Did you see this is the condition !
Since I have arrived , all this has been going on .
What is it ?
An ailment or something else .
The one who told her that she is upstairs , but she was not .
That 's our patient .
What did you say her name was ? - Radha .
Adha . - Radha , and not Adha . - Radha ...
This journey has clogged my mind ,
First I will have to clear it then it will work .
Where is my other bag ?
Where did my other bag go ?
Whoever has done this , I 'll not leave him .
One day I 'll nab him .
Wow ! - Hey , stop !
Where is he going ? He 'll die . Look !
Mr. Ramlal , where are you going ?
We are going to Shahpur .
Since when .
Has Mr. Yagyaprakash returned from London or not ...
... we are going to see that .
You can come along if you want .
Yes , come on , come on we will have a lot of fun .
Not from here , the door is at the back .
Sunder sweet-maker .
Did you get married ?
Okay , you are going along with sister-in-law .
Give me my bequest .
Priest , close the door we are getting late . Greeting .
We 'll give you money later . Shut the door .
Come on , let 's hurry !
Seems like he has gone mad seeing Manjulika .
Taj mahal is right in front .
Junior priest , are you doing penance sitting here ?
Pushpa , where are you going on your donkey ?
Pushpa !
I am Murari , and not Pushpa .
Have you heard , Manjulika has entered Radha 's body !
People say that my behaviour has changed .
Take a look at my face , tell me how do I look ?
Adit , what are you searching for ?
Where is the bathroom ?
All the ways look similar . Name all the paths .
There goes king Siddharth road .
There goes queen Avni road .
That 's Radha Square . Where is the bathroom ?
It is not that difficult ?
After taking a right and a left ,
the door that you will see in the front ...
... that is the bathroom .
But what will I wear ?
The dirty clothes have been taken for washing the clean clothes ...
... have been burnt .
What should I wear ?
No , this is my house .
Do one thing , take a bath I will send a loin-cloth for you ...
... wear that today . - Okay .
" Hail Shiv Shankar . "
" Neither the thorn nor the stone pierces you . "
" I have drunk this in your name . "
Who has taken my clothes ?
These had been sent for me .
Who are you ? - Who are you ?
In my house you are asking me who am I ?
How dare you ?
You are that impostor of the morning return me my clothes .
I have worn it , and it is a bit drenched too . - What ?
Do one thing , wear my towel .
You pig , bloody serpent . You wore my clothes .
What good will abusing do ? What will I wear ?
Give it back .
Take the towel off and come out , I want to see you properly .
Scoundrel , useless , how dare you !
Great , you look beautiful .
Are you peeking inside ?
Go !
Golden tresses , your tresses touch your knees . Wow .
May you rot , don 't you have respect for women ?
One thing is for sure , we will have to meet ...
... and there is no need to circulate that .
I want to meet you , and that too alone .
You scoundrel , swine , may you rot to death .
Aren 't you ashamed flirting with a lonely girl ? Return my clothes !
Quiet ! Here ! Here ! Wear it !
Who is it ?
Is someone there ?
Where is it ?
" I am yours . "
" I am only yours . "
" My desires will remain in the breeze . "
" It will stay alive , even after being destroyed . "
" I am yours . "
" I am only yours . "
Marbles ?
Wait ! Wait !
Wait ! Wait ! Wait !
What are you doing here ?
What ? - Bathroom .
Will you do it here ? - Yes ...
... Here , will you do it here ? - No , in the bathroom .
Why did you run seeing me ?
That ... - What ?
I couldn 't control it .
What , you couldn 't control your urine in the stomach .
Now it has come out , the pant is wet .
No . - Then ?
Let me , I have to go badly .
And what of I would have been hurt badly . - What ?
You don 't know .
No . - You don 't know .
Come on , let 's urinate .
Come on . - I will do it .
Come on . Hurry ! Start pissing .
Come fast .
Start , come on .
I saw it , small one .
Small one .
It is not good to roam around all night , understood .
What happened , aren 't you done yet ?
Is it Niagara falls ?
Small one .
Hey , small one ...
Adi .
Adi , get up .
Thank you , what happened ?
Did you sleep here the entire night ?
Yes , the program was quite long .
Program , which program ?
Tell me one thing , who knows Bengali here ?
No one .
But Radha had maybe studied for some years in Kolkata .
Does she know classical music ?
Does she know how to dance ? - No .
Then who was dancing all night wearing the anklet ? - Where ?
On the third floor .
You heard it .
Heard it , but the artists door was closed I couldn 't see her .
By the way , who sleeps there ?
Nobody .
And now the lock there is broken too , no one goes there .
Can we go up and take a look .
Yes .
But if someone sees us , then there will be a commotion .
Nothing will happen , no one will know .
Come on , let us go . - Yes . Just a minute .
Ok . It 's done .
So this is that haunted closed room .
About which Siddharth had told me about .
So he is the flirt king .
Look , look cruelty can be seen on the face . He is a scoundrel .
Even the painter couldn 't hide it .
Look at his eyes , bad intentions .
Full of lust , it can be seen clearly .
And where is the other party ?
The other , that Bengali dancer .
Do you have her photograph ? - Come , I will show you .
Adi . - Yes .
Look .
Oh God .
No wonder the old king was besotted , its my mistake forgive me .
Why are you saying that ?
What a girl ? ! What a girl ? !
I don 't have any complaints with that old king ...
... that he snatched from that Shashidhar .
Do you want to see Shashidhar 's house ?
What ? - Do you wish to see Shashidhar 's house .
Yes , show me . Then come .
Look .
Okay , so from there Shashidhar used to look at Manjulika ...
... and from here Manjulika used to sing seeing him . That ...
" I am yours . "
" I am yours . I am only yours . "
- Come here , I will show you something interesting .
" I am only yours . "
Look , look her sari .
Which she would wear while dancing .
And ...
look , this pearl necklace . This arm band .
So many jewels , which I have never seen or heard of .
Look , anklets .
Where is it , it should have been a pair .
" I am yours . "
" I am only yours . "
Did you find it ? - No .
Let it be , it is just an anklet not a big thing .
It must be lying somewhere around . Forget it .
Wait ! - O God !
Wait ! Wait ! Wait ! Wait ! Wait ! Take your pants off ? - What ?
Where is this sound coming from ?
Wait , wait , wait .
Here .
Where did you get this anklet from ?
In the passage outside .
So you are the one that dances the entire night upstairs . - No .
Then why do you keep it in your pocket ?
That ... - What 's that ?
I wanted to wear it and see ... - You want to become a woman .
No . - Then ?
I mean . - What do you mean ?
I wanted to keep it in the pocket ... - What ?
If the other anklet can be heard or not .
Detective , you want to be a detective . Wow
Are these anklets yours ?
Do you have any objection if I keep it ? ... No .
Go , go , go . Go and sleep .
Small one .
Small one ...
How are you , Radha ?
Why were you peeking in here last night ?
Is this a part of your treatment too ?
You can think whatever you want ?
Whatever you will think , I will like it .
Then why have you come here now ?
I was just accounting , that when I added subtracted and multiplied ...
... and then I even divided it , I got only one answer .
And maybe it was right too .
But now I am thinking , there is nothing wrong ...
... in adding subtracting multiplying and dividing it .
What ? What ? What ?
Foolish girl .
I was just accounting , that when I added subtracted and multiplied ...
... and then I even divided it , I got only one answer .
And maybe it was right too .
But now I am thinking , there is nothing wrong ...
... in adding subtracting multiplying and dividing it .
Can I ask you something ? - Ask .
Do you need treatment too ?
What was he doing here ?
Nonsense , I didn 't understand anything .
Be careful , because as soon as he arrived he tried on me .
Useless , ox , goon .
Can such a fool can ever be a doctor ?
Look , look , look , look .
I think you should think about your second marriage . Come on .
Siddharth cannot even think about anyone else other than me .
But you are wrong in one matter , I can prove that . What ?
Where did you find these ?
These are Manjulika 's .
These , these are Manjulika 's
It must be 50-60 years old . - Yes .
Why not , these are just 2 years old .
Hers must have been lost by now .
These are real . They are not real , they are fake !
How do you know ?
Because I am an archaeologist , and I have read old things .
I agree that you are ajunk seller , but I know a bit too .
They are fake . - They are real .
Fake . - Real .
Your eyes are deceiving you .
Deceit , my eyes , my eyes .
Okay , you win , it is useless arguing with you . Now come on .
You win .
Excuse , you will it is useless arguing with you .
What are you arguing about ?
Nothing , ask your barney .
She thinks she knows everything .
I have done nothing all my life .
" I am yours . "
" I am only yours . "
" My desires will remain in the breeze . "
" It will stay alive , even after being destroyed . "
" I am yours . "
" I am only yours . "
" My darling , my heart will go on to you even after death . "
" My heart will look for you in restlessness . "
Who is it ?
Who is it outside ?
It 's me , king Vibhutinarayan !
Scoundrel , open the door !
Open the door !
Who are you ?
Scoundrel , you ask me who am I ?
I am Manjulika .
Why have you come here ?
I have come to kill you !
I have come to kill you and drink your blood !
Open the door ! - You will kill me !
You will kill me !
You cannot kill me , forget it !
I will kill you !
I will kill you before the Eight day of the Goddess Durga veneration !
Only after that I 'll be at peace .
Scoundrel Open the door !
You will kill me on the Eight day of the Goddess Durga veneration !
Yes !
Then come on the Eight day of the Goddess Durga veneration !
Go from here now .
I am going ! I am going for now !
But I will return to kill you .
I will return to murder you .
Go from here , go .
Mummy ! Mummy ! Mummy !
You have troubled me a lot .
I am playing hide and seek with you .
You come wherever I go . Aren 't you ashamed ?
Come on , come out .
Come out . - What is it ?
Where do you study ? - Economics .
Where do you study ? - Guwahati .
Goti . - Guwahati .
Didn 't you say Goti ?
No really , I said Guwahati .
What are you doing here ?
My holidays are going on ?
Whatever I ask you , you spontaneously answer it .
You are very proud . Why ?
I have been noticing that ...
wherever there is a doubt you are always there .
Tell me the truth , do you act in the college .
Do you imitate people ?
Do you know Bengali ?
Then why were you singing in Bengali last night ...
... in a girls voice ?
I am yours .
I am only yours .
Why were you singing ?
It wasn 't me . - Then was it your guest ?
Why do you keep roaming around in the night ?
Don 't you feel sleepy ?
You want to urinate .
Where do you bring so much urine from ?
We don 't have so much .
And where do you keep it ?
Did you fill up this pond ?
Looking at you I can say something is wrong .
Tell me the truth or else I will hypnotize you .
Then I will know all the secrets in you .
Tell me . Tell me quickly .
Even I want to find out , who is doing all this .
Or else , all of you will turn sister Radha mad .
Are you mad ? You are crying .
I didn 't know it isn 't allowed to joke in this house ?
Here .
I never saw such a sensitive boy .
Enough now . Relax ! Relax now .
No , no , no don 't cry son .
Come on , wear this I will show you something . Come on .
Come on , don 't cry .
Chandu , now I am going to tell you something .
Don 't take it as ajoke .
It is dangerous to roam around in the palace at night .
There is danger at every step .
Danger means its life threatening .
You can lose your life . There can be a murder too .
Yes . It can really happen .
If not today then tomorrow .
But it will happen , and before the Eight day of ...
... the Goddess Durga veneration !
And yes , only you and me know this .
Don 't tell anyone else . Understood .
But what will we do now ?
Do you trust me ? - No .
Good , now we will go together . - Where ?
Malikapur .
Malikapur ? - Do you know where the village is ?
Yes , it is exactly at the centre of our country . Good .
But it is very far from here .
Wherever it is , we are going .
Understand , come ... come .
" Come on traveller . "
" The journey of life is unknown . "
" Our span of life is unknown . "
" Neither do you know nor do I. "
" Still we are going on an unknown destination . "
" Allah be with you , Allah be with you Allah be with you . "
" Allah be with you , says every moment . "
" Come on traveller . "
" Every view , every sign is new . "
" Who knows where the dawn is ? "
" Each part , each moment is new . "
" No one knows where we will dwell . "
" Every city , every path is new . "
" Every sign , every moment is unknown . "
" Neither do you know nor do I care . "
" We are going towards unknown . "
" Allah be with you , Allah be with you Allah be with you . "
" Allah be with you , says every moment . "
" Come on traveller . "
" Allah be with you , Allah be with you Allah be with you . "
" Allah be with you , says every moment . "
" Come on traveller . "
Greetings . - Greetings . Greetings .
Mr. Yagyaprakash Bharti has sent us here .
Has he returned from London ?
Yes , and he received your message .
He has started studying the horoscopes that you have sent him .
He will arrive here one day ...
before the eight day of the Durga veneration .
Because the auspicious date of the veneration ...
... has been fixed on the eight day of Durga veneration .
This is the list of things required in the veneration .
Read it carefully .
All the things that are required in the quantity and quality ...
... you will have to keep it ready .
That means there is some danger .
All the members of this house have to be alert .
The servants should be alerted too .
If someone is ill , take special care of them .
Why are you standing outside , come in . - No , we are leaving .
At least have tea .
We are not even supposed to have water of this house .
Okay . Greetings .
Did you hear what they said , until the veneration is done ...
... we will have to take care of Radha .
She is under the control of the ghost , how can we control her ?
It is easy , tie her up in a sack .
You should be tied up .
Or sealed in the wall like Anarkali .
Have you come on your own will ...
... or did the government there send you here .
A ghost has come from America , to catch a ghost
Brother .
Brother , brother Badri .
You are making tea .
Please make some for Siddharth . - Please !
Okay . And give me some flour , today I will bathe with flour and see .
I will just bring it .
Here .
From tomorrow you will have to give a written request ...
... only then will you get tea , understood . - Sorry .
I am going , Siddharth is going on the site ...
... and as usual has forgotten the car keys . - Okay .
Nandini . - Coming sister .
Give it to brother Siddharth . Ok . - Ok .
Tea , tea , tea .
Sister has asked me to give it to brother Siddharth . - Okay .
Chandu , take all the heavy things . - Okay .
Knife , dagger , scissors , take everything .
Look , take this knife .
And yes , give me this knife .
Nice .
Give me , leave it .
Why are you taking all this ?
We are going for a shootout in Lokhandwala .
Here . Keep this .
And how will I cut the vegetables ? - With your teeth .
Do one thing , put her teeth and tongue in this too .
Come on , take it .
Let father find out , then see .
What happened ?
Siddharth !
What are you doing Aditya ?
Rat kill , in your tea .
How do you know ?
Can you see the bottle , it is empty .
I just saw the tea utensil , there was poison spilled all over .
What nonsense ? - Nonsense !
Then do one thing , drink the remaining tea .
You will find out after you die .
Who , who will mix the poison ?
The one who made you tea ?
Ask Nandini , who made this tea ?
What is all this going on ?
Sister Radha asked me to give this tea .
But there is poison in the tea ...
Lock up Radha in the room . - Why ?
Because your daughter is mad .
If you don 't lock her up in the room ...
... then there will be deaths in this house .
Remember what I am saying !
What status do you have to accuse my daughter ?
Get out of my house !
Get out of here . - Keep your emotions in control , uncle !
He is a doctor , he knows more about this matter than all of us !
And if she is not inane , then why did she mix poison in the tea ?
Do you have an answer to that question ?
To hell with your question .
I will not keep my daughter locked up .
Brother Badri , I know what you are going through .
But it is for everyone 's betterment .
And then it is foolishness to invite death .
What are you saying uncle , I am not mad ...
I have to decide that and not you !
Leave me , leave me !
Leave my daughter ! Leave her !
I say ... Control your emotions ! - Leave me ! Leave me !
Save me , father save me ! Today there was poison in the tea ...
... if something happens then .
Go inside . Leave me .
No one will open this door without my permission
It is dreadful .
Whatever you are doing , it is very dreadful .
What I am doing is for the betterment of everyone .
Why are you all after me ?
What have I done ?
Better than making me suffer like this , kill me !
Poison me , or burn me alive .
All of you are cowards . Don 't you have the courage !
Fine , I know what I have to do !
Radha ! Don 't do that Radha !
Don 't be mad Radha !
Aditya ! Open the door Aditya !
Please open the door . Please ...
Repeat after me whatever I say .
" Om I am making this offering to the water . "
I perform so many venerations still this happened to my daughter .
Now my daughter will not remain ...
... locked up in that room like an animal .
Today I will open the lock .
Both of you support me .
Now do the veneration .
After you finish the veneration send the donation in our office . Ok ?
They are saying in the village that ...
When there is madness in the house ... - What ?
They can break the alliance out of fear .
And there hasn 't been any engagement too .
They won 't do that , maybe .
Radha 's ailment cannot affect Nandini ...
... you don 't have blood relation with her .
Beware , don 't you say that again .
People don 't think before blowing matters out of proportion .
Even I care about Nandini Batuk Shankar .
I will talk to his father and fix the engagement .
Mummy ! Mummy .
Who are you ? Who are you ?
I am the junior priest of the temple on the high hillock .
So what should I do ?
I have heard that some mad doctor from Africa ... has arrived
Is that you ? - Yes I am , so ?
I have a suspicion . - Then play it .
That I am mad . - Who says it ?
People say that I look changed , what do you think minister .
I am a doctor and not a minister .
Forget that , but have I really changed ?
Yes there is something wrong ?
Then treat me .
Come after the Durga veneration , go .
Go , go , go
Hey listen .
Stay back .
Stay away from water , water is dangerous for you .
Ok . Thank you . - Go , go , go .
Water .
The army has returned .
" Our eyes locked . "
" The conversations gave rise to more conversations . "
" I swear on Lord , beloved our meetings will be beneficial . "
" Our eyes locked . "
" The conversations gave rise to love . "
" I swear on Lord , beloved our meetings will be beneficial . "
" Let 's rock now , beloved . "
" Come on , let 's dance beloved . "
" Slyly from the clouds . "
" The moon is looking here . "
" To see the face of my beloved . "
" What beauty is . "
" Slyly from the clouds . "
" The moon is looking here . "
" To see the face of my beloved . "
" What beauty is ! "
" The day passes in your thoughts . "
" I cannot sleep at nights . "
" Your innocence , your love makes me suffer every moment . "
" A strange fun has taken over . "
" The time to meet has come . "
" Now there won 't be any distance or any loneliness . "
" Mad girl . "
" You slyly . "
" Sometimes by raising and lowering your eyebrows . "
" Took my heart . "
" Let 's rock now , beloved . "
" Bride , listen bride the wedding night has arrived . "
" Bride , listen bride our blessings are with you . "
" I couldn 't find peace . "
" It is just your intoxication . "
" Wherever I saw , it was just you . "
" I want to say , I don 't want to stay away from you . "
" My companion , I don 't want to experience the pain of distance . "
" I was floored my dear . "
" I became crazy for you . "
" How can I tell you how much I love you , you didn 't know . "
" Let 's rock now , beloved . "
Where is Avni ? - She must be somewhere around .
Let 's look for her . - Why are you so tense . - Come on .
Come on , come fast .
Avni ! Avni ! - Avni !
Avni ! - Avni !
Avani ?
Look there .
Avni ! - Avni !
Avani !
Listen .
Avni ! Avni !
Siddharth !
Siddharth , stop it ! Leave him !
Did you see what he was doing to her ?
Didn 't you see ?
Listen to me !
Siddharth , stop it !
First take care of Avni , then we will deal with him !
First take care of Avni ! Go .
Aditya , I didn 't do anything please listen to me .
I know , I understand , I know .
Tell me , what do you want to say ?
The ghost of the palace is none other , but Avni .
What nonsense ?
Whatever I tell you , you will have to listen ...
... with a lot of patience and concentration .
The one who tried to kill Nandini and burnt Avni 's sari ...
... that was your Avni and not Radha .
The day ... I arrived I understood that
Radha is not sick then , who can it be ?
That day when I went to the 3rd floor along with
Avni for the first time .
The excitement with which she was talking about Manjulika ...
... I noticed restlessness in her which only a mental patient has .
I got a kind of a psychic vibration .
You mean to say that Avni is insane .
No ! No !
Whereas , every common people call any mental ailment insanity .
The brains have different sections .
However a person may appear from outside ...
... because of the levels of these sections of the brain .
Whereas the heart of the people function differently ...
... in different situation .
In psychology we call it conscious , sub-conscious and unconscious mind .
Avni 's ailment is such , that sometimes she forgets ...
... herself completely and becomes Manjulika .
This ailment is called disassociative ...
... identity disorder .
That means , a person dawning the identity of another person ...
... forgetting themselves .
Avni who has studied in America starts speaking Bengali ...
... which she has never learnt .
She doesn 't know how to dance , but when she turns into Manjulika ...
... she starts singing and dancing .
She even knows when you sleep .
When you are in deep sleep .
And exactly at that time she roams around the palace as Manjulika .
That 's why people in old times used to call it acquired by ghosts .
But such mental and physical strength is the wonder of nature .
Why Avni has this ailment , to know that I asked you ...
... to stay close to Radha in the temple .
Do you remember ?
I wanted to know if Avni is jealous of Radha or not .
But no .
On the other hand her entire concentration was on our argument ...
... whether this anklet is real or not .
Then I saw her inferno in her angry eyes ...
... as if Manjulika is speaking .
To know the condition in which Avni was brought up ...
... I went to her village along with Chandu .
To know more about her childhood life ...
I met with her relatives , her friends , her teacher .
She was 3 years old , when her parents left her ...
... with her grandma and went to America to try their fate .
Child Avni surely would miss her parents ...
... but for her , grandma was everything .
Her grandma would tell her stories of ghosts , fairies ...
... and magical tales , and Avni 's loneliness would disappear .
So she started believing that good always triumphs over evil .
But old grandma started not keeping well ...
... so Avni 's parents came to take her home .
She was in the 10th started .
Her exams were very near .
But her mind was restless with papa 's decision .
She was not ready to stay away from grandma .
This mental tension was erupting in her like a volcano .
Avni was sitting in the exam hall ...
... when suddenly she tore the exam paper and threw it ...
... and she ran away from the school screaming like mad .
That was the first break down of her brain .
The papa didn 't delay at all to take her to America .
They took her forcefully .
And after some days they received the news that grandma passed away .
With growing age , Avni forgot her childhood .
Years later , when she came here with you ...
... she lost herself in the story of this palace .
Like she used to get lost in grandma 's stories .
She felt like Manjulika 's saga as her own .
The separation of two lovers because of a king and then death .
Avni started having sympathy with Manjulika .
Because the injustice that was done to Manjulika ...
... the same thing has happened to Avni in her childhood .
She wanted the triumph of Manjulika 's truth ...
... over the kings cruelty .
The sympathy grew so much that Avni started thinking ...
... that she is Manjulika .
The ailment that was hidden in Avni 's mind ...
... it started coming out .
And then , all the incidents that took place ...
... it must have happened like this .
Since when do you know Avni ?
One months love and then marriage .
Then it was impossible for you to have such deep information about her .
But why did you lock up Radha ?
The day she mixed poison in the tea , I saw Manjulika ...
If Manjulika would have overpowered Avni ...
... then it would have been impossible to bring her back .
To divert her attention , I had to put the blame on Radha .
Now except for the three of us , even Radha knows everything .
When I told Radha about Avni 's ailment ...
... that innocent girl said , to save Avni she is prepared ...
... to pose as a mad girl all her life .
Siddharth ! Siddharth , open the door .
Siddharth , open the door .
Who locked this door , Siddharth ?
Siddharth , who closed this door ?
And look , the sari that I wore in the wedding .
How did this happen ?
Maybe Radha must have done it .
Yes , it must be her .
But why is she doing all this ?
We shouldn 't have brought her out of the room .
But when did she do all this ?
I cannot remember anything .
When did you come ?
Avni , he is the groom .
Yes .
I ... am not feeling well .
Yes , it is quite late and all the rituals are over ...
... so let sister-in-law go .
During the mental ailment , Avni turns into Manjulika ...
... you become Shashidhar and ...
... Siddharth becomes the old king for her .
Whatever she did that day , it was all a part of it .
The onlooker will feel that you forced Avni ...
... and in that way your marriage will break and Manjulika ...
... will get her lover back .
Manjulika is slowly overpowering Avni .
In the next two days , that is on the 8th day of the Durga veneration ...
... Avni will completely transform into Manjulika .
Manjulika had taken an oath that she will never let any king live .
And in Avni 's view , Siddharth is the king here .
That 's way she can kill Siddharth any time .
If she fails in that , then she might commit suicide like Manjulika .
If I save Avni , then I will have to risk Siddharth 's life .
If you have to save Siddharth , then Avni will lose her life .
No matter what I do , someone is certain to die .
Greetings high priest . - Greetings .
I wanted to ask you something .
I have been very restless since two days .
I will feel better if we talk .
Shall we go in ?
Was your daughter 's engagement ceremony fine ?
Yes , very nicely . Why ?
It was a very ominous moment .
Some obstructions would come , such arrangements were made .
No , nothing of that sort happened .
Okay , if nothing happened then it 's the grace .
I had sent the list of things . - Yes .
What about it ? - It is ready .
Good . - But Radha ...
There is a barrier in Radha 's horoscope too ...
... but I am not worried about that .
Her mind is restless .
Saturn ...
The Saturn is creating an obstruction ...
As soon it changes , everything will be fine .
But I feel some problem ...
There is a problem in this palace .
It has already started too .
There is a grave chance of someone 's untimely death .
Death , whose ?
I have seen him somewhere .
You must have seen him in some mental asylum .
I can 't remember .
Teacher you forgot , try to remember .
America , parapsychology conference .
You had given a speech .
Exorcism , the Indian way .
Aditya ! Aditya Shrivastav ! Yes .
They seem to be long lost .
Son how can I forget you .
I never hoped to see you here , that 's why I was shocked .
Badri Narayan , when this fool is present here ...
... then why did you call me for your daughter ?
Seems like you don 't know him properly .
He is a famous psychiatrist .
Don 't be fooled by his appearance ...
... he looks like a wanderer , but he his like Raavan .
With ten brains . - Teacher .
He is the right hand of the world 's ...
... famous psychiatrist Dr. Elise . Teacher .
He is the writer of parapsychology 's two famous articles .
Teacher , I want to talk to you .
Yes , say .
Not here , somewhere else .
Mr. Badri , please keep two chairs outside . - Yes .
Okay .
Son , don 't get me wrong .
But with my entire experience , and the affection that I have for you ...
... I am warning you .
This case has no solution , it has no treatment .
It is incurable .
Teacher , I respect your experience ...
... but in this matter , all the books
I have read and my knowledge is useless .
You know teacher , psychology is the only science without a definition .
Every mind is different , every heart is different ...
... every key has a different lock .
For my friend , I have to use a way ...
... which no psychologist in the world might have used .
You know I have to go beyond the ...
... conventional concepts of psychotherapy .
Try it , I will not stop you .
But what will you do ?
Avni is a girl that has grown up hearing stories ...
... of ghost , fairies and other magical tales from her grandma .
I will need the weapon of your ...
... mantras to control her mind .
Can you create an ambience
for me like getting rid of a ghost from a body ...
Okay .
Move ahead with self-confidence , I am with you .
It is starting from a very dangerous point .
Before Avni turns completely insane
I want to make her aware that she is ill ...
But ... - She won 't be able to tolerate it .
She might lose her senses .
You are afraid of that isn 't it ?
But I have decided , not me but Siddharth will make her realise ...
... that she is a mental patient .
If she can tolerate that incident , then we have some hope .
I don 't know whether I am doing wrong or right .
I just need the power of your prayers .
That 's all . - Bless you .
Avni is getting ready to go out to buy jewellery along with Nandini .
Go in her room and stop her .
But I haven 't stopped Avni for anything .
But today you will have to do it .
Stop her , she will argue , be stubborn don 't let her go .
Possible that her expressions might change .
Don 't be scared , call her with all your love and affection .
Call her back .
I will be around the room .
Go , stop her .
Avni . Where are you going ?
I had told you , I am going to buy jewellery for Nandini .
Avni , don 't go .
Why ? Don 't you want me to go ?
But I had told you in the morning .
Then why are you stopping me now ?
I must have said it at that time , but I am stopping you now .
Why , what is the problem if I go to buy jewellery with Nandini ?
I had told you .
Yes , but now you will not go .
Why , why can 't I go ?
Because I said no .
You won 't let me go !
You will not let me go !
So you will not let me go out from here !
Even today you dare to stand in front of me !
Today is 8th day of Durga veneration !
I have to cut your throat and drink your blood !
I have to dance on your corpse !
Avni !
What did I do , Siddharth ?
Nothing .
No , I surely did something .
I said something , isn 't it ?
I said something wrong , isn 't it ?
Something strange .
Siddharth I am feeling strange .
Something strange is happening within me .
Siddharth , I am very scared .
There is something wrong with me , Siddharth isn 't it ?
Don 't hate me please .
Siddharth , I am feeling very tired .
Siddharth I want to rest .
Aditya !
What are you doing with my Avni ?
You are handing her over to a foolish sorcerer .
Listen to me . You don 't have to say anything .
I have seen ! I have seen my Avni .
Relax Sid !
I will take my Avni to America , to London !
I will take her to the biggest doctors in the world ...
... but I will not let you treat her .
Listen to me , I want to say something .
I have heard enough !
Now I don 't want you to treat her !
Fine , go . Take her wherever you want to !
But remember one thing , no psychiatrist or medicine ...
... cannot bring your Avni back to you .
Even I can do what other big psychiatrist can do .
I can make Avni a new .
But what 's the use .
She will living statue , what else
But just a statue .
She will walk .
Will that be enough for you ?
Is it enough ?
Siddharth , I want you to get back your Avni .
With her sweetness , her passion .
But for that I need a day .
Then take all the days you want , but return me my Avni ,
To say the truth I am going to experiment something ...
... I just have to do that .
It is possible that Avni might attack you , may injure you ...
... she might do something that you never forget ...
Do whatever you wish too .
Kill me , I 'll not mind it .
But she should be cured .
I just need her .
Just return me my Avni .
I will try Siddharth . I will try .
Sir has arranged everything for the prayers .
But Manjulika , I mean Avni .
We will have to bring Avni there .
And only Sharad can do this job .
" I am just yours "
" I am yours . "
" My desires will flow with the breeze . "
" They will stay alive , even after being destroyed . "
" I am yours . "
" I am just yours "
" Beloved , even after death I will love you . "
" In restlessness my heart will seek you . "
" My tresses have your fragrance . "
" I cannot live without you . "
" You are immersed in me . "
" Your voice can be heard in the clinking of my bangles . "
" This separation always brings us closer . "
" Beloved . "
" I am yours . "
" I am just yours "
" Your tunes are immersed in my breath . "
" My life is nothing without you . "
" Your voice plays in my heart . "
" Your desires can be seen in my heart . "
" You are the only thing I ever think about . "
" The moment of separation is very difficult . "
" Beloved . "
" I am yours . "
" I am just yours "
Leave me !
Scoundrel , goon !
I will behead you !
I want to drink your blood !
Who are you ?
I will not tell you !
I will never tell you !
You won 't tell me !
Tell me . Tell me !
Manjulika !
I am Manjulika !
Sit there .
Sit .
Sit !
Why have you come here ?
I will kill him !
Whom ?
Take his name .
Evil , I will kill the evil king !
Today is the 8th day of Durga veneration !
I will cut his throat and drink his blood !
I will help you in killing the king .
But after that you Manjulika , will leave Avni 's body forever .
Accepted .
Promise .
I promise you !
I want to take revenge !
Here ! Kill him !
You can hear me .
You are Avni .
Avni .
Tell me who are you ?
Tell me your complete name
Avni Siddharth Chaturvedi .
Avni , now you are a happy person .
Happy and calm .
Yes .
You know the truth that you are completely cured .
I know .
If that 's so , then Avni is about to wake up .
Slowly , slowly , slowly ...
... Slowly , slowly , slowly .
Do you recognise us ?
Why are you asking that ?
Avni , you had an ailment .
A very strange , interesting ailment .
But I cured that ailment .
It won 't trouble you again .
I take guarantee of that .
I can understand .
I know I trust you Adi . Thank you .
By the way , whenever you want to know what happened with you ...
... then Siddharth will tell you everything leasurely .
Just think it is a story and listen to it . Ok .
It 's not necessary .
I know everything .
How many people have done a favour on me .
But I am indebted to Siddharth ...
... for loving me so much .
And for tolerating my insanity .
Okay .
I completed all my promises .
Go , take her away . Go .
I completed one thing , except for one thing .
I have to complete that too before I leave . - What ?
It is something personal .
Radha .
Radha the world knows it is difficult ...
... to live with insane people .
But it is impossible to live with psychiatrists .
Do you want to try ?
I think you will manage just fine .
If I have your permission , shall I send my parents to you ?
Excuse us , we got you wrong .
No , no there is nothing like that .
You did the impossible .
You had come to get rid of the palace 's ghost ...
... but you cured two lives .
Please bless me .
Girls don 't touch the feet .
One incident ailed you and other cured you .
And if the time is right , everything becomes fine .
I didn 't do anything .
Everyone is fine , except for you .
Come I will cure you . Come .
Look at me .
Open your eyes .
Stick out your tongue .
Now you will be absolutely cured . Ok .
How do you feel ?
I felt as if something came out of my ears .
Fantastic , now you are fine .
Okay , good bye . So can I bathe now ?
You didn 't take a bath till now .
You had asked me to keep away from water .
Go , and take a bath go .
Thank you , I am cured . - Go .
I am cured .
How can I apologise to you ?
You are elder , don 't apologise .
Just do one thing , I have asked someone something .
If she agrees , then don 't refuse , just bless us .
Okay , I will leave .
Good-bye .
" Where she at , I am searching for that fine shorty . "
" And it ain 't , that I am being naughty . "
" I am for real , you know I don 't play that . "
" Because I mean it , when you hear me say that . "
" Madly searching for this shorty . "
" In my world , the number one haughty . "
" Everywhere she makes me go crazy . "
" Your eyes are a maze . Your talks are confusing . "
" In my dreams , I keep looking for you baby . "
" Your eyes are a maze . "
" Your talks are confusing . "
" In my dreams , you keep me driving me so crazy . "
" You stay in my heart . "
" He is perfect , talk to me ... "
" My restlessness says . "
" I keep praying , all day all night long . "
" Hail Ram , Hail Ram . "
" Hail Krishna , Hail Ram . "
" You are my silence . "
" You are my intoxication . "
" You are my saga . "
" Making me so happy by shaking her body ... "
" You are my wandering image . "
" You are my desire . "
" You are my beloved . "
" Everything about you , baby I like it ... "
" Your tresses are like a dream world for me "
" I find peace only in your arms . "
" My only wish is that if I ever , ever could make you mine . "
" Everyone pray with me now , all day all night long . "
" Hail Ram , Hail Ram . "
" Hail Krishna , Hail Ram . "